24studio.co.uk 2012-06-25

# Studio - Home Shopping / Catalogue Shopping - buy personalised gifts

[](javascript:history.go\(-1\))

* * *

* * *

## Privacy Policy

* * *

(i) When you order we will ask for your name, e-mail address and delivery address. These details will enable us to process your order and contact you in the event of any queries. We will also ask for your telephone number, so that we can contact you urgently if necessary in the event of any problem with your order. We will communicate with you by e-mail, telephone or letter. 

(ii) We may also use the information we hold to notify you occasionally about important changes to the web site, new Express Gifts Limited services and special offers. We may invite you to take part in market research. If you would rather not receive these notifications or invitations, please [contact us](https://www.24studio.co.uk/ss/help/websuite_faq.jsp?curtab=contact) or send an e-mail to [contact@24studio.co.uk](mailto:contact@24studio.co.uk). 

(iii) When you enter a competition or prize draw, we will ask for your name, address and e-mail address so that we can administer the competition and notify the winners. We may also ask for further information for marketing purposes. You do not have to provide this information in order to enter the competition or prize draw. 

(iv) Other carefully selected companies may also make further offers to you. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please [contact us](https://www.24studio.co.uk/ss/help/websuite_faq.jsp?curtab=contact). 

(v) You have the right to ask for a copy of the information we hold on you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. 

(vi) We reserve the right to store shopping pattern data in order to provide a better service for our customers. We may occasionally use some of the information we hold for the purposes of testing our internal systems. Such testing is only carried out where necessary, and your information will be treated with the utmost care and respect. 

(vii) By using our site you consent to the collection, retention and use of this information by Express Gifts Limited. Any changes to our privacy policy will be notified on this page. 

(viii) We work with third-party data analytics and advertising companies. Some of these companies may use anonymous information (but they do not collect or use any personally identifiable information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements or provide data based on which we may provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Learn more about this practice or about your choice to opt-out of this practice: [Struq privacy policy & opt-out [new window]](http://www.struq.com/privacy_policy.html), [Criteo privacy policy & opt-out [new window]](http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy), [Google privacy policy & opt-out [new window]](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/privacy/), [Coremetrics privacy policy & opt-out [new window]](http://coremetrics.com/company/privacy.php). 

For more information about cookies and how to control which cookies you allow, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org/ new window](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).   
For more information about behavioural advertising, visit [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/ new window](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/). 

24studio is a trading style of Express Gifts Ltd.   
Registered Office: 2 Gregory Street, Hyde, Cheshire SK14 4TH  
Registered Number 718151  
VAT No. : 125688644  
Express Gifts is authorised and regulated by the Financial Services Authority.  
Our customer service number is 0871 200 0378.  
Please use the [contact us](https://www.24studio.co.uk/ss/help/websuite_faq.jsp?curtab=contact) link to contact us securely or send an e-mail to [contact@24studio.co.uk](mailto:contact@24studio.co.uk). 

top of page
